Jack Taylor

jack-t-taylor@outlook.com www.linkedin.com/in/jack-t-taylor www.github.com/jahreja A confident, diligent final year Fine Art student with a passion for uniting contemporary creativity with technology. Capable and experienced in a variety of fields spanning both the arts and computing, with additional strengths in communication and organisation.

Technical Skills

- JavaScript, ES6 - HTML5 - CSS

- Python - MongoDB - Express.js

Node.js
 Version Control (Git)
 Adobe Creative Suite

- Adept programmer, with a clear, consistent style and an intuitive, imaginative approach to project planning and problem-solving.
- Acute sense artistic composition and design, proven through interdisciplinary fine art outcomes on an exhibition level.

Personal Skills

- Confident Collaborator working in teams has always been a fundamental aspect of both my academic and
 personal life. My university course has allowed me to undertake key leading roles in four art exhibitions over
 the last few years and collaborating with peers is at the heart of the studio practice at The Glasgow School of
 Art, and I am comfortable operating in a range of roles, both as a part of a team and under my own initiative.
- Driven and Motivated Learner while my course has provided the facilities to produce work, it has been my
 responsibility to direct the work itself. Philosophy, maths and physics have all played crucial parts in my
 practice, having self-taught the required knowledge. This passion has carried through to my technical side,
 quickly teaching myself a range of skills including painting, 3D modelling, and an array of programming
 languages.
- **Flexible and Organised** my self-driven working style goes hand-in-hand with efficient, practical time management. This has been highlighted over the past year, with a successful adaptation to a self-directed artistic practice in a home studio environment throughout the pandemic.

Education

The Glasgow School of Art Lancaster Royal Grammar School

2017-2021 2010-2017

Course: BA(Hons) Fine Art A-Levels: Mathematics, Art. French

Predicted Grade: First Class Honours GCSEs: 6A*, 4A, B

Hobbies and Interests

- Keen sports fan and an avid runner, organising a charity running event in 2020 raising over £8,000.
- Deep love for music, hosting a tri-weekly radio show in 2020 and playing multiple instruments.

Previous Work Experience

- Front of House Staff, Red Peppercorn Restaurant, Lancaster [2016-2017]
- Sports Hall Caretaking Assistant, *Lancaster Royal Grammar School* [2015-2016]